{
    "subject": "resource/Ricardo_Bofill",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Spain",
    "human_readable": "Ricardo Bofill was born in Spain.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8764940500259399,
            "question": "Where was Ricardo Bofill born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8698931932449341,
            "question": "Is Ricardo Bofill Spanish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.836956799030304,
            "question": "Was Ricardo Bofill born in Europe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.699032187461853,
            "question": "Is Spain considered Ricardo Bofill's home country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6132546067237854,
            "question": "What is known about Ricardo Bofill's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.601814866065979,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Ricardo Bofill's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5733701586723328,
            "question": "What country is Ricardo Bofill from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5639444589614868,
            "question": "In which nation did Ricardo Bofill originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4551085829734802,
            "question": "What is the name of the country where Ricardo Bofill was raised?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3496236503124237,
            "question": "Where did Ricardo Bofill spend his early years?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ricardo Bofill was born in Spain.",
            "html": "dbpedia_383_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the country where Ricardo Bofill was raised?",
            "html": "dbpedia_383_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which nation did Ricardo Bofill originate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_383_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Ricardo Bofill from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_383_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_383_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_383_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_383_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_383_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_383_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_383_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_383_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_383_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_383_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_383_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, Ricardo Bofill was indeed born in Barcelona, which is located in Catalonia, Spain. This information supports the triple \"Ricardo Bofill was born in Spain\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide multiple mentions that Ricardo Bofill was born in Barcelona, which is a city in Spain. Therefore, the statement \"Ricardo Bofill was born in Spain\" can be considered correct based on the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}